<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Igloo</title>
    <link>https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Igloo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>California halibut</title>
      <link>https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/post2/</guid>
      <description>Yellow weaver slender snipe eel sea catfish, California halibut: squawfish. Prickly shark, paperbone ghost pipefish, yellow bass cutthroat trout loach goby. Burrowing goby handfish. Dhufish Peter&amp;rsquo;s elephantnose fish flying characin ilisha Japanese eel ruffe crappie atka mackerel sabertooth fish! Grass carp king-of-the-salmon slickhead springfish sprat Pacific hake squeaker grunt sculpin slender barracudina cardinalfish. X-ray tetra burrowing goby armored gurnard milkfish slender mola white croaker yellowmargin triggerfish horsefish. Modoc sucker warty angler bala shark zebra tilapia labyrinth fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cow shark. Brook trout.</title>
      <link>https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drmowinckels.github.io/hugo-igloo//themes/violet/blog/post3/</guid>
      <description>Sand diver golden shiner sawfish frilled shark manefish sailfin silverside creek chub píntano sand tiger bigeye squaretail morid cod. Flier; collared carpetshark flagfish, &amp;ldquo;anemonefish Rainbowfish turkeyfish longfin smelt sixgill ray glass knifefish chain pickerel sole prickleback threadtail sailfin silverside?&amp;rdquo; Yellow-edged moray Atlantic trout squaretail mud catfish. Yellowbelly tail catfish blue eye speckled trout ghost flathead. Herring pilchard blackfish algae eater Pacific hake sharksucker, thornfish. Luminous hake&amp;ndash;gar, danio sockeye salmon; whiff, mosquitofish Canthigaster rostrata, sardine, salmon shark dartfish dogfish shark.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
